whynotad.com 2010-12-30

# Whynotad Privacy Policy | Free Ads Advertising Classifieds Worldwide Wiki | www.whynotad.com

Privacy Policy  

We have designed this site to be user friendly and as quick and trouble-free as possible. We care about your privacy and are committed to ensuring that your personal information is protected. We will NEVER sell your personal information.   

What information do we collect ?

We ask basic information, in order to create your ad and an account for you. We may use your e-mail address to verify the account and to occasionally send you news and updates about our exciting Web 2.0 Portals. 

Apart from what you provide, we do gather automated information every time you visit - information such as your IP address, what Internet browser and operating system you're using, the time and date of your visit and other statistical information. This is the general information that web servers collect whenever you visit a website.

If you're particularly worried about this, then there's lots of resources and companies that can help you stay anonymous online. To find out more, just search online at Google.

If there's anything about our privacy policy that you're unsure about or need us to clarify, then please contact us.   

You should from time to time check back for any updates or changes to our terms and conditions.   

We'll endeavor to keep our policies updated to make sure that they are as clear as possible.

Further Information

We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. 

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies go to the Google Double Click Dart Site http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx
